Guide to the Stanford University, Board of Trustees, Meeting Records SC1010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records created prior to 2010, 1885-2009; Series 1
  - Supporting material, 1905-1976, 1998-2009; Subseries 3; 28 Linear Feet (56 boxes)
    - 2005 Jun
      - Remember Stanford (Office of Planned Giving) (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - SCIR (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Trustee ballots (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - 2005 Oct
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Athletics (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Commission on Graduate Education (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Development Committee (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Faculty (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Finance Committee (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - Hennessy, Looking Backward, Thinking Forward, Reflections on 2000-2005 and the Future (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - Medical Center Committee (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - Trustee elections (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - The University ("The 21st Century University"; copy of the founding grant, etc.; Administrative Guide Memo on University Organization) (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - 2005 Dec
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Committee of the Whole (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - East Palo Alto Schools (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Finance Committee (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Medical Center Committee (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous [memo re dinner; "Rising Above the Gathering Storm" – prepublication copy of the executive summary of the National Academies] (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Office of Technology Licensing (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - President (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - 2006 Feb
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2027.
      - Academic departments and schools (GSB, Engineering, Earth Sciences (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Athletics (football) (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Campaign Steering Committee (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Commission on Graduate Education, Report of, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Finance Committee (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Hennessy, Looking Backward, Thinking Forward, Reflections on 2000-2005 and the Future (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Land and Buildings Committee (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Medical Center Committee (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - National Survey, David Demarest; key findings from a national survey of 500 opinion elites in the U.S., conducted January 6-19, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Stanford University 2005 Annual Report (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Trustee ballot (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - 2006 Apr
      - Athletics (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Campaign for Undergraduate Education Final Report (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Campaign Roster (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Committee of the Whole (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Enterprise Risk Management and Disaster Preparedness (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Expendable Funds Pool and Endowment Payout (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Infection Control/Pandemic (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Medical Center (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous (H&S handout, trusteeship items and Hoover Board elections) (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Parking and Transportation (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - SCIR [Special Committee on Investment Responsibility] (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - 2006 Jun
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Budget Plan 2006/2007 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Compensation, Committee on (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Finance Committee (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Medical Center (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous [includes letter from Zev Kvitky, president of USW, fact sheet from Institute for Research in the Social Sciences, and SU Commencement Week Schedule] (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Trusteeship, Committee on (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - 2006 Oct
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Commission on the Future of Higher Education (US Secretary of Education) (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Development Committee (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Finance Committee (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Hennessy, Accomplishments in 2005-6 / Goals & Challenges for 2006-7 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Medical Center (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - The Stanford Challenge [campaign booklet] (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - June 2006: Main Medical Center Replacement Study Progress Report (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - 2006 Dec
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Athletics (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Bio-X Program (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Committee of the Whole (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Development Committee (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Finance Committee (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Medical Center (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous (includes Housing Purchase Programs for Faculty; article on Compensation of University Presidents) (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Office of Technology Licensing Annual Report (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Overseas Studies Annual Report (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - SCIR [Special Committee on Investment Responsibility] (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Trustee ballot and other Trustee matters (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - 2007 Feb
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2028.
      - Academic Policy (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - Ad Hoc (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - Alumni and External Affairs (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - Annual Report 2006 (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - Development Committee (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Finance Committee (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Medical Center (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous (includes booklet on "Twelve Principles of Governance That Power Exceptional Boards"; and "The Path to Climate Sustainability, a Joint Statement by the Global Roundtable on Climate Change" (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Orientation to the Stanford Indirect Cost "Crisis" and Its Legacy [incorrectly dated Feb. 13, 2006] (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Stanford Challenge (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - 2007 Apr
      - Land and Buildings (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Metrics (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous academic (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Retreat, Information Packet (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Retreat, Additional Matters (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Retreat, "Dynamics of Higher Education in the US" (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Stanford Globalization Workshop, Summary Binder (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - 2007 Jun
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Athletics (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Budget Plan 2007/08 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Development Committee (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Finance Committee (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Investment Responsibility (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Medical Center (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - 2007 Oct
      - Trusteeship (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Athletics (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Development Committee (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Finance Committee (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Hennessy, Accomplishments in 2006-7, Goals & Challenges for 2007-8 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Medical Center (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Trusteeship, Committee on (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - 2007 Dec
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Athletics (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Development Committee (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Finance Committee (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Medical Center (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - 2008 Feb
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2029.
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Development Committee (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Finance Committee (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Medical Center (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - S.U. Annual Report 2007 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Trusteeship (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - 2008 Apr
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Annual Report and Budget Plan (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Athletics (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Building on Excellence; a Guide to Recruiting and Retaining...Faculty (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Finance Committee (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Retreat on Future Scenarios (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Special Committee on Hospital Replacement and Renewal (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - 2008 Jun
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Athletics (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Budget Plan 2008/09 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Development Committee (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Finance Committee (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Globalization Task Force (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Medical Center (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Trusteeship (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - 2008 Oct
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - Athletics (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 55, Folder 23)
      - Development Committee (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Economic Impact Study 2008 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Faculty issues (2 SU publications) (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Finance Committee (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Hennessy, Accomplishments in 2007-8, Goals & Challenges for 2008-9 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Medical Center (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous (includes 3 resolutions and NY Times article on Drugs and Disclosure) (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Student Mental Health and Well-Being Task Force Report, October 2008 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Task Force on Undergraduate Expansion (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - 2008 Dec
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Finance Committee (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Medical Center (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - 2009 Apr
      Restricted until Jan. 1, 2030.
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Athletics (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Finance Committee (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Medical Center (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous: list of "Influential Blogs and Social News Sites" (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - 2009 Jun
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Budget Plan 2009-2010 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Global Committee (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 56, Folder 26)
      - Medical Center (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - 2009 Oct
      - Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Athletics, Task Force on (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Bing Overseas Studies (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Development Committee (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Finance Committee (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Hennessy, John. Looking Back and Looking Forward (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Medical Center (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous (includes Who's Who) (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - 2009 Dec
      - Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Athletics, Task Force on (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Finance Committee (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Financial Aid Update (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Globalization (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Investment Responsibility, Special Committee on (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Land and Buildings (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Medical Center (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - 1893 Jun (Box 58)
  - Agendas and supporting material from Board of Trustees administrative office, 1991-2000; Subseries 4; 15 Linear Feet
    - Agendas and supporting material, 1965-1998; Accessions ARCH-2002-315 and ARCH-2003-211; 10.5 Linear Feet (7 boxes)
      - Agreement between the Board of Trustees of Leland Stanford Junior University and United Stanford Workers Local 680, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Board of Trustees meeting agenda and supporting documents, 1992 Feb (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Board of Trustees meeting agenda and supporting documents, 1992 Apr (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Board of Trustees meeting agenda and supporting documents, 1992 Jun (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
      - Board of Trustees meeting supporting documents, Land and Buildings committee, 1992 Jun (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1992 Oct (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1992 Dec (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1993 Feb (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
      - Committee on the Medical Center meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1993 Mar (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1993 Apr (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1993 Jun (Box 1, Folder 16-18)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1993 Oct (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1993 Dec (Box 1, Folder 21-23)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1994 Feb (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
      - Committee on Land and Buildings, 1994 Feb 8 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1994 Apr (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1994 Jun (Box 2, Folder 6-10)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1994 Oct (Box 2, Folder 11-13)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1994 Dec (Box 2, Folder 14-16)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1995 Feb (Box 2, Folder 17-19)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1995 Feb (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1995 Apr (Box 3, Folder 2-5)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1995 Jun (Box 3, Folder 6-11)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1995 Oct (Box 3, Folder 12-16)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1995 Dec (Box 3, Folder 17-19)
      - Joint meeting, alumni trustee selection, 1995 Dec (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1996 Feb (Box 3, Folder 21-23)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1996 Feb (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1996 Apr (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1996 Apr (Box 4, Folder 4-6)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1996 Jun (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1996 Jun (Box 4, Folder 9-11)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1996 Oct (Box 4, Folder 12-16)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1996 Oct (Box 4, Folder 17-20)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1996 Dec (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1997 Feb (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1997 Feb (Box 5, Folder 5-8)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1997 Apr (Box 5, Folder 9-11)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1997 Apr (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1997 Jun (Box 5, Folder 14-19)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1997 Jun (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1997 Oct (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1997 Oct (Box 6, Folder 4-7)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1997 Dec (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1997 Dec (Box 6, Folder 10-12)
      - Joint meeting, alumni trustee selection, 1997 Dec (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1998 Feb (Box 6, Folder 14-17)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1998 Apr (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1998 Apr (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
      - Stanford Management Company, Board of Directors meeting, agenda, 1998 Apr 6 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1998 Jun (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1998 Jun (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
      - Stanford Management Company, Board of Directors meeting, agenda, 1998 Jun 11 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, meeting agenda and supporting documents, 1998 Oct (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1998 Oct (Box 7, Folder 13-15)
      - Stanford Management Company, Board of Directors meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1998 Oct (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1998 Dec (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1998 Dec (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Stanford Management Company, Board of Directors meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1998 Dec (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Regional planning of the Stanford Campus, 1985 Sep (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - "Academic Decision-Making and Planning Processes" discussion paper (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Letter/Report from Hoover Overseers to Warren Christopher, 1965 Aug 16 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Centennial Campaign Prospectus, 1985 Aug 26 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Board of Trustees potential agenda items, 1985 Sep-1986 Jun (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Minutes, 1975 May 13 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Agendas and supporting material, 1998-2000; Accession ARCH-2004-145; 4.5 Linear Feet (3 boxes)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1998 Dec (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1999 Feb (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1999 Feb (Box 1, Folder 6-9)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1999 Apr (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1999 Apr (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
      - Stanford Management Company, Board of Directors meeting, agenda, 1999 Apr (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1999 Jun (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1999 Jun (Box 1, Folder 17-20)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1999 Jun (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1999 Jun (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
      - Stanford Management Company, Board of Directors meeting, agenda, 1999 Jun (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Board of Trustees, School of Humanities and Sciences 50th Anniversary, 1999 Jun (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Board of Trustees special meeting, additional materials, 1999 Sep (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1999 Oct (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1999 Oct (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
      - Board of Trustees, Committee on Nominations, 1999 Oct (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Stanford Management Company, Board of Directors meeting, agenda, 1999 Oct (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 1999 Dec (Box 2, Folder 15-19)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 1999 Dec (Box 2, Folder 20-22)
      - Board of Trustees, Committee on Nominations, 1999 Dec (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Stanford Management Company, Board of Directors meeting, agenda, 1999 Dec (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 2000 Feb (Box 3, Folder 3-5)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 2000 Feb (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
      - Board of Trustees, Committee on Nominations, 2000 Feb (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, agenda and supporting documents, 2000 Apr (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
      - Board of Trustees meeting, additional materials, 2000 Apr (Box 3, Folder 11-13)
      - Board of Trustees, Committee on Nominations, 2000 Apr (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Stanford Management Company, Board of Directors meeting, agenda, 2000 Apr (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Joint meeting, alumni trustee selection, 2000 Apr (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Records created since 2010, 2010-2015; Series 2
  Arrangement note
  Board of Trustees meeting records created since 2010 are arranged by meeting date. Agendas, minutes, and supporting documents for each meeting are filed together.
  Restricted for 20 years from creation date.
  - Individual meetings
    - 2010 Feb 8-9
      Restricted until Sep 1, 2031.
      - Supporting Materials: Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Supporting Materials: Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Materials: Athletics, Task force on (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Supporting Materials: Audit and Compliance Committee (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Supporting Materials: Finance Committee (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Supporting Materials: Globalization Task Force (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Supporting Materials: Institute for Creativity and the Arts (Box 1, Folder 7)